{"data":[{"question":"Nothing but necessities ___ in the shop.","a":"are sold","b":"is sold","c":"are going to sell","d":"were sold","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense \n- Subject: (necessities) is plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"What ___ when I phoned you last night? \"I _________ my papers and was starting to take a bath.\"","a":"had you done, just finished","b":"did you do, just finished","c":"are you doing, have just finished","d":"were you doing, had just finished","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense, when\/before + simple past","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"Those children ___ themselves on the beach when the rain ___ and spoilt their fun.","a":"had enjoyed, was coming","b":"were enjoying, came","c":"were enjoying, was coming","d":"enjoyed, is coming","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Use the Past Continuous to indicate that a longer action in the past was interrupted. The interruption is usually a shorter action in the Simple Past. \n+First blank: simple past continuous tense \n+Second blank:Simple past tense ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"I turned around and saw that everyone ___ at a woman who ___ in a strange language.","a":"staring, shouted","b":"stared, shouting","c":"was staring, was shouting","d":"was staring, shouting","answer":"3","explain":"\n- First blank \n+ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n+Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch part of the action \n- Second blank: past continuous tense: \n+When you use the Past Continuous with two actions in the same sentence (stare-shout), it expresses the idea that both actions were happening at the same time. The actions are parallel. ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"You look very busy. I ___ you _________ hard for your task.","a":"suppose, work","b":"suppose, are working","c":"am supposing, are working","d":"am supposing, work","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Fist blank: \n+ Simple present tense: The Simple Present can also indicate the speaker believes that a fact was true before, is true now, and will be true in the future \n- Second blank: - Sometimes, we use the Present Continuous to say that we are in the process of doing a longer action which is in progress; however, we might not be doing it at this exact second ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"Once you _________ used to the customs here, you ___ this place.","a":"get, probably liked","b":"get, will probably like","c":"had got, probably liked","d":"will get, probably like","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Get used to: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Second blank: simple future: express the idea of a general prediction about the future.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"One of Professor Chen's works ___ translated into English in 1980.","a":"were","b":"was","c":"are","d":"would be","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense : express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (1980)\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"A large amount of money ___ spent on the decoration.","a":"has","b":"have","c":"has been","d":"have been","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: (We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now) + Passive vocie ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"A lot of trees ___ on each side of the road.","a":"grow","b":"stands","c":"are grown","d":"is standing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Grow: if plants grow, they exist and develop in a natural way \n- Subject (trees) is plural \n- Simple present","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"We have sold many mobile phones of this kind and the rest ___ on sale today.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"have","d":"has","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The rest= mobile phones which is plural \n- Simple present","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"}]}